(people chattering)
(tires screeching)
(birds squawking)
♪ I'm not a perfect person ♪
♪ There's many things I wish I didn't do ♪
♪ But I continue learning ♪
♪ I never meant to do
those things to you ♪
♪ And so I have to say before I go ♪
♪ That I just want you to know ♪
♪ I've found a reason for me ♪
♪ To change who I used to be ♪
♪ A reason to start over new ♪
♪ And the reason is you ♪
♪ I'm sorry that I hurt you ♪
♪ It's something I must
live with everyday ♪
♪ And all the pain I put you through ♪
♪ I wish that I could take it all away ♪
♪ And be the one who
catches all your tears ♪
♪ That's why I need you to hear ♪
♪ I've found a reason for me ♪
♪ To change who I used to be ♪
♪ A reason to start over new ♪
♪ And the reason is you ♪
♪ I'm not a perfect person ♪
♪ I never meant to do
those things to you ♪
♪ And so I have to say before I go ♪
♪ That I just want you to know ♪
♪ I've found a reason for me ♪
♪ To change who I used to be ♪
♪ A reason to start over new ♪
♪ And the reason is you ♪
♪ I've found a reason to show ♪
♪ A side of me you didn't know ♪
♪ A reason for all that I do ♪
♪ And the reason is you ♪
(sirens wailing)